[Music]
[音乐]
hi everyone thank you for that
大家好，谢谢你
introduction you've officially made it
介绍你已经正式做到了
to the last session of the day so
到一天的最后一个环节
congratulations thank you for your
恭喜你谢谢你
interest in being diligent in coming
勤于学习的兴趣
coming listen listening to our talk
来听我们的谈话
so as Lara said I'm George Saab I have
就像劳拉说我是乔治·萨博
the distinct pleasure of being the
成为的独特乐趣
person who runs the java group at oracle
在oracle上运行Java组的人
i'm also the chairperson of the open JDK
我也是开放JDK的主席
governing board and I'll have to show
董事会，我必须证明
you this which says if you're going to
你这说如果你要
make decisions about buying things we're
做出购买我们所要买东西的决定
gonna be talking about stuff that's
会谈论的是
happening in the future
将来发生
so keep that in mind you know things
所以请记住，您知道一些事情
change that's what this slide is about
更改此幻灯片的内容
ok so the way we're going to do this I'm
好，所以我们要做的方式是
going to talk just a little bit about
只是谈一点
Java in general and kind of what's going
Java的总体情况和发展趋势
on and then Michael is going to talk a
然后迈克尔要谈一个
whole bunch about some of the projects
关于一些项目的整堆
that we're currently working on I think
我目前正在研究
I suspect in this room there are a lot
我怀疑这个房间里有很多东西
of people who use Java a lot and so I
很多使用Java的人，所以我
may not you know need to twist your arm
可能不知道需要扭动手臂
or convince you of why Java SE is
或说服您为什么选择Java SE
important obviously we think it's a
很明显，我们认为这很重要
great technology you know my group is
伟大的技术，你知道我的团队是
one that came from Sun Microsystems and
一个来自Sun Microsystems，
has been working on java for many many
已经为许多人开发了Java
many years and so it's something that
很多年，所以这是
we're passionate about and we love
我们充满热情，我们热爱
speaking with people who use the
与使用
technology and you know we love hearing
技术，你知道我们喜欢听
success stories we're all true
成功故事，我们都是真实的
interested in hearing about challenges
有兴趣了解挑战
you have so we're always happy to be at
你有，所以我们总是很高兴在
conferences like this and I hope you'll
这样的会议，我希望你会
take advantage of that I think you know
利用我想你知道
when we think about Java and how it has
当我们考虑Java及其如何
evolved one of the things that we always
进化了我们永远的一件事
try to be conscious of is having an
尝试意识到有一个
evolution which is very thoughtful and
进化是非常周到的
not haphazard Java has never been a
并非偶然Java从来都不是
technology that's been sort of chasing
一直在追逐的技术
the latest features and just kind of
最新的功能，只是
tacking things on the side we really try
在我们真正尝试的一面解决问题
to make sure when we add something that
确保当我们添加一些
we understand what it's good for why you
我们了解为什么对您有好处
might want it we go
可能想要我们走
through a lot of work to basically do
通过很多工作基本上可以做到
our development of new features now in
我们现在在开发新功能
the open in open JDK and so this is
在开放的JDK中打开，所以这是
something you can take advantage of you
你可以利用你的东西
can actually go to open JDK you can sign
可以实际去打开可以签名的JDK
up to mailing lists you can see the
到邮件列表，您可以看到
design discussions that we're having as
我们进行的设计讨论
we work on new features and what you'll
我们致力于新功能以及您将要做什么
find if you do that is things that you
找到你是否这样做
think are really simple like you know
认为真的很简单，就像你知道的
they're adding closures to Java how long
他们正在向Java添加闭包多长时间
could that take
那可以吗
it's obvious well you know in fact when
很明显你知道事实上
you look at something like lambdas in
你看着像lambdas这样的东西
Java 8 and it looks obvious that's
Java 8，看起来很明显
because a lot of time and a lot of hard
因为很多时间和很多努力
work has gone into making it obvious I
工作变得很明显我
guarantee you that if we took the first
向您保证，如果我们采取了第一个
design that we had for lambdas and had
我们为lambda设计的设计
run with that we would have had
用我们本来可以的
something out very very quickly but it
东西很快就出来了
would not have felt as natural and it
不会觉得那么自然，
would have had a lot of challenges a lot
会有很多挑战
of problems a lot of frustrations and in
问题很多挫败感和
fact those are the kind of things that
其实那些是那种
tend to actually accumulate when you're
往往会在你
making a technology and you're not just
进行技术开发，而不仅仅是
thinking of you know well how do I get
想着你就知道我怎么得到
it out in six months you're thinking of
在六个月内就想到了
you know how is this going to persist
你知道这将如何持续
you know how is this going to be viewed
你知道怎么看
in five years or ten years how are the
五年或十年后，
things that I do in this feature are
我在此功能中所做的事情是
going to enable us to do new things
使我们能够做新事物
going forward or prevent us from doing
前进或阻止我们做
some of the things we want to do you
我们想要做的一些事情
know those are the sort of deep things
知道那些是深层的东西
that we think about I will say that you
我们想到的我会说你
know when I mentioned the mailing lists
知道我何时提到邮件列表
we also are trying to do these projects
我们也正在尝试做这些项目
with early access binaries so Michael
与早期访问二进制文件，所以迈克尔
will give some links later where you can
稍后会提供一些链接
actually go and download binaries that
实际去下载二进制文件
have you know early access versions of
您是否知道的早期访问版本
some of the features we're working on
我们正在开发的一些功能
now and try them out and until tell us
现在尝试一下，直到告诉我们
what you think because ultimately you
您的想法，因为最终您
know the things that we do we don't do
知道我们要做的事情我们不做
just because they're interesting
只是因为他们很有趣
academic exercises right you know Java
您知道Java的学术练习
is a technology that is very much there
是一种非常存在的技术
to be used and want people to use it and
被使用并希望人们使用它
we can only make it good if you if you
如果你愿意的话，我们只能把它做好
tell us how it works for you in real
告诉我们它如何真正为您工作
life okay so let's see I think you know
生活还不错，让我们看看我想你知道
here too
这里也
very close two and a half decades on you
距离你二十五年半
know we view Java as a technology that
知道我们认为Java是一种
is very relevant and very vibrant you
与您非常相关且充满活力
know it tends to be hard in our industry
知道这在我们的行业中往往很难
for technologies to persist and remain
使技术得以持久并保持
popular but you know we see Java as a
流行，但您知道我们将Java视为
technology that is as relevant today as
今天与之相关的技术
it was 10 years ago as it was 20 years
那是10年前，因为是20年
ago
前
and part of the reason is that we're
部分原因是我们
constantly investing in continuing to
不断投资于继续
solve problems to make your lives easier
解决问题，让生活更轻松
you can see just you know a little bit
你可以看到就知道了一点
of a roadmap there and a nice little
那里的路线图和一点点
little graph from you know one place
你的小图知道一个地方
that measures these kinds of things on
可以测量这些东西
you know the popularity of Java so one
您知道Java的普及程度，
of the areas that we think about a lot
我们经常考虑的领域
now and I'm sure you do too
现在，我确定你也这样做
is javo'''s readiness for the cloud and
是javo对云的准备，
how suitable it is as a technology there
那里的技术有多适合
this is something that you know we're
这是你知道的我们
we're very passionate about and have
我们非常有热情并且有
been actively putting in features
一直积极投入功能
thinking about how could we make the
考虑如何才能使
experience of using Java in the cloud
在云中使用Java的经验
work really really well and there's some
工作真的很好，有一些
interesting aspects of that right I
这项权利的有趣方面
think you know one of the things that we
以为你知道我们其中的一件事
tend to see I you know go and ask people
倾向于看到我你知道去问人
you know well is this important or is
你知道这很重要还是
this important as an example how many
这个重要的例子有多少
think that small footprint and fast
认为占地面积小且速度快
startup time is important I certainly do
启动时间很重要，我当然知道
yeah just about everyone how many people
是的，几乎每个人都有多少人
think that massive heaps and low latency
认为大量的堆和低延迟
are important yeah so if you're doing
是很重要的，所以如果你在做
something like ml or you know AI you
像ml或您知道AI的东西
know you want to be able to handle that
知道你想要能够处理
as well and so you know it's kind of
以及，所以你知道这是一种
interesting right that we have these you
有趣的权利，我们有这些你
know two sorts of problems that in many
知道很多的两种问题
ways are kind of headed in different
方式是不同的
directions and if you ask people which
方向，如果你问别人
one are important they go yeah both of
他们走是很重要的
those so okay great we'll try to do
那些很好，我们会尽力做到的
everything you know we we want to do all
您所知道的一切我们想做的一切
of those things well and I hope that
这些东西很好，我希望
some of the projects we're going to talk
我们将要讨论的一些项目
about today will give you some insight
今天大约会给你一些见识
into some of the things that we're doing
进入我们正在做的一些事情
there okay so Java as a technology is
好的，所以Java作为一种技术是
something that is as popular as it is
受欢迎的东西
today because many vendors take part
今天，因为有许多供应商参与
in its development this has been true
在发展中，这是事实
pretty much since the beginning since we
自从我们开始以来
started on Java at Sun and it is true
在Sun的Java上开始，这是事实
today we do our development in open JDK
今天，我们在开放式JDK中进行开发
and a nice thing about that is you can
一件好事是你可以
actually see check-ins happening you can
实际看到签到发生，您可以
see reviews happening you can basically
看到发生的评论，您基本上可以
go and see who's doing what and I think
去看看谁在做什么，我认为
you know that's kind of a nice way to
你知道这是一种很好的方法
get some insight into where the
深入了解
investment is coming in towards job as
投资正朝着工作方向发展
it is today and and towards the future
今天和未来
of Java and so as you can see there
Java的基础，如您所见
there quite a few folks that take part
有很多人参加
the reality is most of the investment
现实是大部分投资
that is happening today is coming from
今天发生的事情来自
Oracle so that's that's good to know
Oracle，这就是很好的了解
these are the projects that we're going
这些是我们要进行的项目
to go through in a little bit here I
在这里经历一点
wanted to first mention I know one of my
想首先提一下，我知道我的一个
colleagues down in the in the show floor
同事们在展厅里
said that he was getting a lot of
说他得到很多
questions from folks about the release
人们对发布的疑问
cadence and the support model so I'm
节奏和支持模型，所以我
happy to answer questions about this you
很高兴回答有关您的问题
might have later either at the end of
可能稍后在
the session or tomorrow I think the
会议或明天，我认为
important thing to understand is that in
要了解的重要一点是
the past we had a model with a very very
过去我们有一个非常非常
long time between releases and so
两次发布之间的时间较长
basically what would happen is we would
基本上会发生的是我们会
go and kind of you know sit under iraq
去吧，有点你知道坐在伊拉克下
and work on stuff for a long time and
并长期从事研究工作，
then we would sort of come out with
那我们就出来
something that was you know pretty big
你知道的东西很大
often you know had very major changes
通常你知道发生了很大的变化
and was often quite disruptive and a
并且经常是破坏性的
result of that was that it often took a
其结果是，通常需要一个
long time for people to adjust to that
人们需要长时间适应
disruption and to you know take their
破坏，你要知道
applications and move them up to the
应用程序并将其移至
next version or start to write new
下一个版本或开始写新的
things that were taking advantage of of
利用的东西
things in those new versions what we
这些新版本中的内容
have done and in fact we did as of two
已经做了，实际上我们从两个开始
years ago is we have moved to a model
多年前是我们已经转向模特
where we release very frequently so we
我们经常释放，所以我们
have new versions that come out every
每个都有新版本
six months and of course we're not
六个月，当然我们不是
we haven't sort of waved a magic wand
我们还没有挥动魔杖
and all of a sudden we can do you know
突然之间我们可以知道
two or three years of work in six months
六个月内工作两三年
instead what we're doing is having
相反，我们正在做的是
incremental releases that have a lot
有很多增量版本
less in them and we still have the same
他们少了，我们仍然有相同的
dedication that we've always had to
我们一直必须付出的奉献
compatibility and to being able to go up
兼容性和能够上升
to new versions but by having these
到新版本，但有了这些
smaller increments it becomes easier for
较小的增量将变得更容易
you with your application to move
您与您的应用程序一起移动
forward right so our goal here has
前进权，所以我们的目标是
really never have big disruptive
真的从来没有什么大破坏力
releases that take multiple years
发行需要多年
instead take the innovation that we're
取而代之的是我们
doing and get it in your hands much more
做并掌握在手中
quickly and so basically the way that
很快，基本上就是这样
this this model works is that the latest
这个模型工作的是最新的
release is always free
发布永远是免费的
so our binaries that we produce directly
所以我们直接产生的二进制文件
from open JDK are available under an
从开放的JDK中可以找到
open-source license under GPL v2 with
GPL v2下的开源许可证
class path and then basically you can
类路径，然后基本上
always just upgrade okay for people who
总是对那些
would like the luxury of staying on an
想要住在一个豪华的
old version for you know years and years
你知道的旧版本
and years as you know many many
和你所知道的很多年
corporations do you know we offer LTS
公司，您知道我们提供LTS吗
release or long-term support release
发布或长期支持发布
it's very similar to you know what you
非常类似于你知道你在做什么
see in in the Linux community where
在Linux社区中看到
basically you will get updates that
基本上你会得到更新
don't have new features that don't have
没有没有的新功能
changes to the language or api's that
更改语言或api
just have essentially stability
基本上具有稳定性
performance and security fixes and so
性能和安全修复等
the intent of that is that those are you
目的是那些是你
know quite easy for you to if you have
如果有的话，对你来说很容易
something running you know a lot of
跑步的事情你知道很多
people have an application they wrote
人们有他们编写的应用程序
years ago they have it running
几年前，他们正在运行
production they just wanted to keep
他们只是想保持生产
running right they're perhaps not doing
他们可能没有做正确的事
a bunch of active development on it that
一堆积极的发展
that's what this is very suitable for
这是非常适合的
and in fact that's a model that has
实际上，这是一个具有
existed for Java pretty much since the
自从
beginning right it was exactly the same
从一开始就完全一样
for Java 6 and Java 7 and now that is
适用于Java 6和Java 7，现在
the case for Java 8 and 11 and going
Java 8和11的情况
forward with these six-month releases
六个月后发布
there will be one of those effectively
将会有一个有效的
every three years right so that gives
每三年就可以
you a choice you can choose to take your
您可以选择拿走您的
application and move forward as new
申请并像新一样前进
come out or you can choose to to do the
出来，或者你可以选择做
long term support with us or with
与我们或长期合作的支持
another vendor there are plenty of
另一个供应商有很多
people out there you know as I mentioned
正如我所提到的，人们在那里
earlier who are you know trying to do
你较早知道你想做什么
active support for Java one thing I'd
积极支持Java我想做的一件事
say to keep in mind if you're if you're
说要记住，如果你是
considering where you want to get Java
考虑要去哪里买Java
updates from is that chart I showed you
是我向您显示的图表的更新
before of who's doing the work right and
在谁做正确的工作之前
so the main thing there is you if you're
所以主要的是你，如果你是
going to get updates from someone you
会从你的人那里获得更新
want to know that they're the ones who
想知道他们是谁
know the technology really really well
非常了解这项技术
this model has been received pretty well
这个模型已经收到很好
you can see quote here from from James
你可以在这里看到詹姆斯的报价
governor I think the there are a lot of
州长，我认为有很多
people who sort of talk about this but
那些谈论这个但
don't talk about the actual pricing so I
不要谈论实际的价格，所以我
think you know some people have come to
以为你知道有人来了
me and said well they have an impression
我说很好，他们有印象
that Oracle is very expensive
甲骨文很贵
we actually base the pricing on this to
我们实际上基于此定价
try to make it simple and easy and
尝试使其变得简单和容易
inexpensive but kind of scale with your
价格便宜，但与您的规模
usage so so we looked at other kinds of
用法，所以我们看了其他种类的
software that people use in a similar
人们在类似情况下使用的软件
way to Java to sort of understand what a
用Java的方式来了解什么
reasonable model would be you can see
合理的模型是你可以看到
the prices here $25 per month on the
这里的价格每月$ 25
server and two dollars and 50 cents for
服务器和2美元和50美分，用于
desktops and it's it scales down with
台式机，它与
volume right so if you have you know a
音量合适，所以如果您知道
thousand servers that's not the price
成千上万的服务器，这不是价格
you're going to pay and in fact the the
您将要付款，实际上
prices for that are on the website if
价格在网站上，如果
you're if you're interested in what the
如果您对什么感兴趣
discounts okay and then with that of
折扣还可以，然后
course you know you you get what all the
当然你知道你得到所有
things you would expect you know years
你期望你知道几年的事情
of support you've got the ability to you
有能力的支持
know call us and have somebody on my
知道打电话给我们，有人在我身上
team right so you get the person who
团队的权利，这样你就可以找到
wrote you know a particular language
写你知道一种特定的语言
feature being able to be the one who's
能够成为
who's doing a fixed for you okay so with
谁为你做固定的
that I'm I want to hand off to Michael
我要交给迈克尔
and he's going to talk about this
他将要谈论这个
project I mentioned earlier we're doing
我前面提到的项目我们正在做
ongoing development thank you George
正在进行的开发，谢谢乔治
oh and I should also say I'm Michael
哦，我也应该说我是迈克尔
Vince that I are on the JBM team at
我曾在JBM团队工作
Oracle I'm gonna talk a bit about the
甲骨文，我要谈一点
products that we are working on I'm not
我们正在研究的产品不是
gonna cover all of them we have I think
我想我会覆盖所有的人
it's like 40 different projects in open
好像有40个不同的项目在公开
JDK told not all of which are being
JDK告诉并非所有事情都在
actively developed but I'll touch on a
积极发展，但我会谈谈
few of the most important ones and it's
最重要的几个
basically the ones in the bubbles here
基本上是气泡中的那些
so the first thing I should say by the
所以我首先要说的是
way is as George mentioned earlier our
就像乔治前面提到的
products are being developed in the open
产品正在公开开发中
if you're curious to see what's going on
如果您想知道发生了什么
if you want to look at the code or play
如果您想查看代码或播放
around with it you can get access to the
围绕它，您可以访问
mailing list you can get the code we do
邮件列表，您可以获取我们执行的代码
publish early access binaries and I have
发布早期访问二进制文件，我有
a slide at the very end with some links
最后有一些链接的幻灯片
and we do really need your help testing
我们确实需要您的帮助测试
things out and giving us feedback on the
事情并给我们反馈
features that we know that what we're
我们知道我们所拥有的功能
doing is actually relevant to you the
实际上与您相关
project's like in the past when we had
这个项目就像过去
these like releases every two two and a
这些就像每两个两个发布和一个
half three years we very much had
三年半我们非常
feature driven releases so we early
功能驱动的发布，所以我们尽早
early on we picked which features should
在早期我们选择了哪些功能
go into a certain release and then
进入某个版本，然后
manager us managers we're running around
经理我们经理我们到处跑
being proactive we expressed up about
积极主动地表达
what was going to happen two and a half
两个半会发生什么
or three years from now right
或从现在起三年后
that can't work you know in a time bound
在一定时间内无法正常工作
release model the one we have right now
发布我们现在拥有的模型
where we do release every six months and
我们每六个月发布一次
it's like on a specific day right so we
就像是在特定的日子，所以我们
need to change our whole way of
需要改变我们的整体方式
developing things so much more of the
开发更多的东西
development now is going on inside
现在正在进行内部开发
projects and those are the ones that
项目，那些是那些
I'll go through and what we try to do
我将经历，我们将尝试做的事情
though is I identified subsets sort of
虽然我确定了一些子集
functionality that can stand on its own
可以独立存在的功能
and deliver that incrementally and more
并逐步提供更多
quickly we're not going to implement the
很快我们就不会实施
whole project before we actually put it
整个项目，然后才实际投入
in mainline right so again a lot of
在主线上，所以再次
these products are being developed on
这些产品正在开发中
the side but like parts of it we're
一边，但像它的一部分，我们
trying to take in actually integrate in
试图吸收实际融入
mainline even if the product then
主线，即使产品然后
continues to live on right so especially
继续过着正确的生活，特别是
for the amber product I'll show a couple
对于琥珀色的产品，我将展示几个
of examples of that the by far biggest
迄今为止最大的例子
and most complicated product that we
还有我们最复杂的产品
have going on right now is Valhalla so
现在要去瓦尔哈拉，所以
this product is looking at adding what
该产品正在考虑添加什么
used to be known until last week maybe I
以前直到上周才知道
shouldn't say what it would use used to
不应该说过去会用什么
be called I'll bring the new term now
叫我现在就来新学期
it's in line types or in line classes as
在线型或线类中
what
什么
that first quiz here so is this type
第一个测验是这种类型的
stateless as in when I've created it can
无状态，就像我创建时一样
I actually go in and change it in some
我实际上进去改变了一些
way is there is there anything in there
那里有东西吗
I can do somebody would mention
我可以做的人会提到
reflection in ignore reflection okay so
反射中忽略反射好吗
the answer is that really it should
答案是确实应该
write everything is final it should be
写一切都应该是最终的
read only there's no way you can affect
只读，您无法影响
this once it's created that's only
一旦创建，这仅仅是
almost correct problem is that every
几乎正确的问题是
instance in Java can be synchronized and
Java中的实例可以同步
you may not think of that as state that
您可能不会认为这说明
lives in the instance but it is there
生活在实例中但在那里
any in any object you have you can you
任何物体中的任何物体都可以
can synchronize on and that's like the
可以同步，就像
hidden state the state that the JVM
隐藏状态JVM的状态
needs to keep in mind and that makes
需要牢记，这使得
this object in some way carry state
这个物体以某种方式携带状态
despite the fact that on the Java level
尽管在Java级别
it sort of doesn't right yeah there are
有点不对，是的
also other subtle things about state or
关于状态的其他细微之处
identity in this case where a single
在这种情况下的身份
instance we actually promise this is
实例我们实际上保证这是
like the in the spec it says if you have
就像规范中的说，如果您有
an instance you can compare it to
一个实例，您可以将其与
another instant the same instance you
另一个瞬间，同一实例
can get this instance in two different
可以用两个不同的实例
ways we're gonna promise you that if you
我们将向您保证的方式，如果您
do double equals on it you get true and
对它做双重等于，你会成真，
what that means concretely is that the
具体而言是
JVM does need to keep a lot of
JVM确实需要保持很多
information about this instance in a
有关此实例的信息
single unique place if I put it that way
如果我这样说的话，一个唯一的地方
in that place is normally on the Java
在那个地方通常在Java上
heap I also have the identity hash code
堆我也有身份哈希码
they're not to be confused with object
他们不要与对象混淆
hash code but same concept same identity
哈希码，但相同的概念相同的身份
piece so what the JVM typically does and
所以JVM通常会做什么
obviously this can depend on your JVM
显然，这可能取决于您的JVM
implementation but what the JVM
实现但是JVM是什么
typically does is that at the top of
通常所做的是
like the very start of every instance on
就像每个实例的开始
the Java heap there's a header and we
Java堆中有一个标头，我们
store all kinds of information in there
在那里存储各种信息
obviously the type of the instance but
显然实例的类型但是
also things like is this object locked
也像这个对象被锁定
and in that case which thread actually
在那种情况下，实际上哪个线程
locked it and things like that now the
锁定它和类似的东西现在
problem that this has is that we do as I
问题是我们像我一样
mentioned need to keep that single
提到需要保持单一
unique instance we need to know exactly
我们需要确切知道的独特实例
which one it is where it is and what
它在哪里，在哪
state it has and that reduces the amount
陈述它的存在并减少数量
of optimizations we can do inside of the
我们可以在内部进行的优化
JVM so for example right now if you have
JVM，例如，如果您有
a JDK and you download it and you create
一个JDK，然后下载并创建
this user-defined point type
此用户定义的点类型
and you create an array of that that
然后创建一个数组
point so we now have a bunch of
点，所以我们现在有一堆
different points on the Java heap it
Java堆上的不同点
will look like this so you'll have a
会看起来像这样，所以你会有一个
number of small instances all the
所有小实例的数量
different points they're spread out
他们分散的不同点
across the heap and then you have an
跨堆，然后你有一个
array which stores pointers to those
存储指向那些指针的数组
individual instances so there are many
个体实例，所以有很多
problems with this the first one being
第一个问题是
if you actually let's say want to
如果您实际上想说要
iterate over all the points you are now
遍历您现在的所有要点
pointer chasing all over the youb so you
指针追逐整个youb，所以你
don't get the cache locality of this
不要得到这个的缓存位置
second thing is that you have all the
第二件事是你拥有所有
headers so now you're you're using a lot
标头，所以现在您正在使用很多
more memory to store effectively the
更多的内存可以有效地存储
information that is only in the end the
最后的信息
x and y-coordinates so what about Halla
x和y坐标，那么汉拿又如何
the product is trying to achieve among
该产品正在努力实现
other things is this I think most of you
其他事情是这个，我想你们大多数人
probably you know this is so obvious
也许你知道这是如此明显
right that why aren't we already doing
对，为什么我们还没有做
this here you have a compact
这在这里你有一个紧凑
representation there's no overhead with
表示没有开销
individual headers if you iterate over
单独的标题，如果您迭代
that array you have everything cache
该数组，您拥有所有缓存
locally and the CPU will prefetch for
在本地，CPU将预取
you all those nice things so why is this
你们所有那些美好的事物，为什么这是
complex well it turns out that this this
复杂的事实证明，这
concept has it requires changes on
概念是否需要改变
everything from the java language level
Java语言级别的所有内容
all the way down to and into the most
一直到最深处
complicated and let's say complex parts
复杂的，比方说复杂的部分
of the vm so it's a very very big
虚拟机的数量非常大
project because it spans all those
项目，因为它涵盖了所有这些
levels and back to what your shells we
级别并返回您的弹壳
take compatibility really really
真的很兼容
seriously so if we could go in and
认真，所以如果我们能进去
change this like put it in the first
改变它就像放在第一个
version of the java spec or like
Java规范版本或类似
overnight we just put this there and
一夜之间，我们只是把它放在那里
everything like we remove everything
像我们删除所有东西
else that was already there right things
否则那已经是正确的事情
would be easy but the problem becomes
会很容易，但是问题就变成了
what happens if you have old code
如果您有旧代码会怎样？
already compiled library code let's say
假设已经编译了库代码
that it's a perfectly you know an
你知道这是完美的
optimal hash map that somebody's done
有人完成的最佳哈希图
for you and you pass in one of these new
为你，你传递这些新的
objects right or the other way around so
正确的对象或相反的对象
we need to think very carefully about
我们需要非常仔细地考虑
that and have a story for what happens
并有个故事
in all those cases because the last
在所有这些情况下，因为最后
thing we want is for Java to evolve into
我们想要的是让Java演变成
something that doesn't look and feel
看起来和感觉都没有的东西
like Java anymore and that doesn't work
像Java了，那是行不通的
with the syntax may look like this this
语法看起来像这样
is subject to change as the like the
可能会像
underscore should make it obvious but it
下划线应使其明显，但它
could be
可能
ECS basically saying in line class and
ECS基本上是在课堂上说
you get this and again like the vm and
你得到这个，就像vm和
the the libraries figure out what to do
图书馆弄清楚该怎么做
for you our tagline for this project is
对您而言，我们对该项目的口号是
codes like a class works like it long
像一类的代码一样长
works like an int meaning you get all
像int一样工作，意味着您得到了所有
the flexibility and the power of java
Java的灵活性和强大功能
classes you can add methods you can do
您可以添加方法的类
computations you can pass them around
计算可以传递给他们
but you get the performance profile of a
但您获得了
simple primitive because we all know
简单的原始，因为我们都知道
that passing it into round that's very
将它传递到圆上
very efficient right and fast from a
非常有效而又快速
like user perspective in most ways the
在大多数方面都喜欢用户角度
only visible change here is it gets a
这里唯一可见的变化是
lot faster so how can we motivate that
快得多，所以我们如何激励
right is how much faster is this like
对的是这样快多少
we've spent I think it's more than five
我们已经花了超过五个
years now easily many man decades on
十年现在很容易许多人
this project already and we still
这个项目已经存在，我们仍然
haven't delivered anything so how can we
还没有交付任何东西，我们怎么能
motivate this project let's look at an
激励这个项目，让我们来看一个
example so we have here matrix
例子，所以我们在这里矩阵
multiplications so it's a simple complex
乘法，所以它是一个简单的复数
class so it's a complex number stored in
类，所以它是一个复数，存储在
the matrix and there are a couple of
矩阵，有几个
operations add and multiply in this case
在这种情况下，运算加法和乘法
they sort of do what you'd expect them
他们做了你所期望的
to do right so they create a new
做正确的事，所以他们创造了一个新的
instance take the value multiplay it
实例取值multiplay
what the other thing and return a new
还有什么其他的东西，并返回一个新的
instance so basically if we want to do a
因此，基本上，如果我们想做一个
multiply again this I copied it from
再次乘以这个，我从
somewhere so I'm sure that somebody has
某个地方，所以我确定有人
verified that the code actually does the
验证代码是否确实
right thing the point is that in order
正确的一点是，为了
to do this you are creating a new
为此，您正在创建一个新
complex a new matrix basically it's
复杂一个新的矩阵，基本上是
you're taking your existing matrixes and
您正在使用现有矩阵
you're creating a new one right and
您正在创建一个新的权利，
there's a lot of pointer chasing in this
有很多指针在此追逐
a lot of allocation going on inside of
里面有很多分配
this code so running this on a JDK today
这段代码，所以今天在JDK上运行
versus running it with the new value
与使用新值来运行
types functionality would look something
类型功能看起来会有些变化
like this and as it says there write
像这样，它说那里写
your mileage may vary and all of that
您的里程可能会有所不同，所有这些
but the point is the boxed version here
但重点是这里的盒装版本
is the existing let's say normal
现有的，可以说是正常的吗
instances and the value version of it is
实例，其值版本为
when you when the VM is free to not
当你自由的时候
necessarily put it on the heap but put
一定把它放在堆上，但把
it in registers locally on the stack and
它在堆栈本地的寄存器中
do all the optimizations without having
无需进行所有优化
to care
照顾
but that identity and all that stuff
但是那个身份和所有东西
right so as you can see the factor here
对，这样您就可以在此处看到因素
it's like twelve times less time it's
时间减少了十二倍
it's a thousand times less memory
少一千倍的记忆
allocated it is three well and then it
分配它是三好，然后
gets more CPU specific but like fewer
获得更多的特定于CPU，但更少
instructions are being executed and
指令正在执行
every instruction actually is faster
每条指令实际上都更快
because there's a lot less waiting for
因为等待的机会少了很多
memory and things like that so pick your
记忆之类的东西，所以选择你的
favorite metric but this is pretty
最喜欢的指标，但这很漂亮
significant right if you can speed up
重大权利，如果您可以加快速度
Java somewhere between two point six and
Java介于两个六点之间
a thousand times we're doing pretty well
一千次，我们做得很好
right so that's why we think this
对，所以这就是为什么我们认为
project is still worth investing in and
该项目仍然值得投资，并且
that's a lots of cool stuff happening
发生了很多很酷的事情
here we have come to the point in this
在这里，我们已经到了这一点
project now that where we are actually
现在投射我们实际所在的位置
not just looking at the existing like
不只是看现有的像
the next milestone or deliverable but
下一个里程碑或可交付成果，但
also looking beyond that how can we make
不仅如此，我们该如何做
sure that whatever we end up with at
确保无论我们最终以
least has some kind of high likelihood
最少有某种可能性
of being future safe in case we want to
为了将来的安全，我们希望
build other things on top of it so for
在此基础上构建其他内容
example it gets even more interesting
例如，它变得更加有趣
when you add generics to this whole
当您将泛型添加到整个
stories what happens if you want to have
故事，如果你想拥有会发生什么
a generic over a a primitive let's stay
一个通用的原始图让我们留下
like an int cool project keep your eyes
就像一个很酷的项目
on it the second product I'm gonna say
关于它，我要说的第二个产品
something about this amber amber is
关于这个琥珀色的琥珀色是
effectively a product that is come made
有效地制成的产品
up of small language improvements so the
小语言改进，所以
tagline for this is right-sizing
标语是正确的尺寸
language ceremony right sizing here does
语言仪式的正确尺寸在这里
not mean stripping Java down the syntax
并不意味着剥离Java语法
down to the point where it's you know
直到你知道的地方
cryptic we still want it to be readable
神秘的我们仍然希望它可读
you read code a lot more than you write
您阅读的代码远胜于编写的代码
it right but it is trying to identify
没错，但它正在尝试确定
the common patterns and make it easier
常见的模式，并使其更容易
to implement code and easier to get to
实现代码并且更容易实现
read the code in the end as well so I go
最后还要阅读代码，所以我去了
through a few of these sub features
通过其中一些子功能
let's say on this project the first one
让我们说这个项目的第一个
being a local variable type inference so
是局部变量类型推断，因此
first a poll how many people here are
首先是民意调查这里有多少人
using Java 8 Java 9 10 11 12
使用Java 8 Java 9 10 11 12
13 okay so how many people have played
13好了，有多少人玩过
around with 10 or later okay a few how
大约10点或更晚的时间还可以
many people have tried var specifically
很多人专门尝试了var
or the local variable type inference
或局部变量类型推断
okay couple of you so the this is one of
好的，你们几个，这是其中之一
those like small things that a lot about
那些喜欢很多东西的小东西
languages already have if you have code
语言已经有了，如果你有代码
that looks something like this so you
看起来像这样，所以你
know normal open some input scream and
知道正常打开一些输入尖叫，
get a stream reader and the buffer
获取流读取器和缓冲区
reader and all that you you probably
阅读器以及您可能拥有的所有内容
recognize this pattern this is pretty
认识这种模式，这很漂亮
much all over the place in Java what you
在Java中到处都有
can see here is obviously that there's a
可以看到这里显然是有一个
lot of sort of duplication we're saying
我们说的是很多重复
the same type is being repeated on both
两者都重复相同的类型
sides and that's sort of you know
双方，你知道
redundant you could argue so what we did
多余的你可以争论，所以我们做了什么
was to implement a feature called local
是要实现一项称为本地的功能
variable type inference which allows you
变量类型推断
to instead of saying the type on the
而不是说类型
left hand side you can just say more now
左手边，你现在可以说更多
this is not making the Java dynamically
这不是使Java动态
typed the only thing this does is to
输入的唯一内容是
have Java C e or whatever compiled
具有Java C e或任何已编译的
you're using to figure out the type on
你用来找出类型
its owns like we could deduce like we
它自己的像我们可以推断出我们一样
know that it says inputstreamreader here
知道它在这里说inputstreamreader
so why do we have to say it again and
那为什么我们要再说一遍
the same thing is true for the java c
Java c也是一样
compiler it can just look at the the
编译器就可以看看
right hand side and you know identify
右边，你知道确定
that it's an input stream reader so I'll
这是一个输入流阅读器，所以我会
sort of put it there you can't later
有点放在那里你以后不能
assign another type to reader here well
在这里为读者分配其他类型
unless obviously it's like a subtype of
除非很明显，它就像是
inputstreamreader
输入流阅读器
you can't like suddenly have it store an
你不喜欢突然有它存储
integer so in this in the background
整数，所以在后台
here this bar actually does sort of
在这里，这个酒吧实际上做了
expand to this right you can it's not
扩展到这个权利，你可以不是
it's still statically typed so this is
它仍然是静态输入的，所以这是
sort of a toy example if you get more
如果你有更多的玩具例子
interesting if we look at something more
如果我们再看一些有趣的话
complex so this you don't absolutely
复杂，所以这不是绝对的
need to understand what this code does
需要了解这段代码的作用
but point at least in in here is that
但至少要指出的是
this line here especially this line here
这条线，尤其是这条线
I'm going to say is so long that I
我要说很久了
couldn't even fit it on a single line
甚至无法将其放在一行上
and you sort of need it there for you
而且您有点需要它
know serving the type information and
知道服务类型信息和
you know getting the type safety but
你知道得到类型安全但是
again it's it's one of those like you'd
再次，这是你喜欢的人之一
rather probably not write that if you
可能不写，如果你
can avoid it it doesn't actually give
可以避免它实际上并没有给
much more information so why not have
更多信息，为什么不拥有
the Java C compiler again or somebody
Java C编译器还是有人
else figure that out for you right so
否则为你找出正确的办法
same thing goes here the after version
之后的版本也一样
using the local variable type inference
使用局部变量类型推断
functionality is hopefully much more
希望功能更多
readable at least I think so and again I
至少我认为是可读的
you you haven't lost like you haven't
你你没有像你没有迷路
lost the type safety and hopefully again
失去了类型安全性，希望再次
this it makes more sense you don't have
这更有意义，你没有
to figure out exactly the you know how
弄清楚你知道如何
to spell that long type name there so
在那里拼写那个长类型的名字
that's one feature from amber another
这是琥珀色的另一特性
one that is in currently in preview mode
当前处于预览模式的一个
so this is something that we've
所以这是我们要做的
introduced recently as well we have
最近也介绍了
preview functionality or preview
预览功能或预览
features they're not enabled by default
默认情况下未启用的功能
they're not yet in the Java spec but
他们还没有在Java规范中，但是
they we have taken them to the point
他们把他们带到了重点
where we are we want to move forward
我们要在哪里前进
with them but before we lock them down
和他们在一起，但在我们锁定它们之前
and actually put them in the spec we
并把它们放在规格中
want some feedback so in order to use
需要一些反馈，以便使用
these we've introduced a couple of
这些我们介绍了几个
options that you you sort of need to opt
您需要选择的选项
in you can't accidentally use this
在你不能不小心使用这个
functionality so you need to say enable
功能，所以您需要说启用
preview and specify a release as well
预览并指定发布
just to make it very clear that you are
只是为了清楚地表明你是
now using something that is a preview
现在使用的是预览
and also at runtime you need to say yes
而且在运行时，您需要说是
enabled via the preview features this
通过预览功能启用
feature is called switch expressions it
这个功能叫做开关表达式吧
is in preview in 12 and we're hoping to
在12的预览中，我们希望
put it in 13 a save as a supported
放入13保存为支持
feature that said we only know what
那个说我们只知道什么的功能
actually is in 13 when 13 ships that
实际上是在13艘船上时
that's new state of the world right now
这就是现在的世界新状况
we're not promising anything until GA
在GA之前，我们不会承诺任何事情
then you know but we're hoping to make
那你知道，但是我们希望
it into 13 so I'm gonna show you an
它变成13，所以我要告诉你
example here where we have there's Anna
这里有安娜的例子
Newman with days and they're well
纽曼有几天，他们很好
there's some place you I hope you will
我希望有一个地方
know it's Rio spelled various ways this
知道是里约热内卢
is a sort of toy example here's a method
是一种玩具示例，这是一种方法
that calculates the number of characters
计算字符数
in the name of the of the day so if you
以当天的名义，如果
doing that using a switch statement so
使用switch语句做到这一点
it's it's doing sort of the obvious
这是显而易见的
thing if the day is Monday Friday or
如果一天是星期一星期五或
Sunday they all have six letters so
星期天他们都有六个字母，所以
that's awesome let's put that in a
太棒了，我们将其放在
variable and
变量和
same for the other weekdays throw an
其他工作日也一样
exception if we find an unexpected day
如果我们发现意外的一天，则为例外
and then finally return the local
然后最后返回本地
variable okay so there are a couple of
可变好吧，所以有几个
problems with this first it's a bit on
首先有问题
the long side you could argue but also
你可以争论的长面也
how do you know like the pattern here is
你怎么知道像这里的模式是
obviously that you are for every case
显然，您适合任何情况
you want to set a local variable define
您想要设置局部变量定义
a local variable and surely there must
一个局部变量，肯定在那里
be a better way of doing this because
更好地做到这一点，因为
now there's a risk that in one of these
现在有一种风险是
cases you actually forget to set it or
如果您实际上忘记设置它，或者
you know you forget to break or whatever
你知道你忘了休息或其他
it is
它是
so what switch expressions do for you is
所以开关表达式为您服务的是
to allow you to treat switch switch
让你来对待开关
statements as if they actually return
好像他们实际上返回的声明
the value as well so in this case it's
价值也是如此，在这种情况下，
more compact there's a new syntax being
更紧凑，有一种新语法
discussed still I should say where you
讨论过，我应该说你在哪里
can say for like these three cases here
可以说这三种情况
there's an arrow syntax and it returns
有一个箭头语法，它返回
six and very specifically what happens
六，特别是会发生什么
then is that the switch as I mentioned
然后是我提到的开关
actually we turn the value so look here
实际上我们把价值变成了，所以看这里
on the on the left hand side and today
在左边和今天
you can't assign the sort of return
你不能指定回报的种类
value from the switch right it's a
开关右边的值是
statement it doesn't return the value
声明它不返回值
but in the new world you can actually do
但在新世界中，您实际上可以做到
that so it does return the value that's
这样它就返回的值是
preview in 12 as I mentioned and then
正如我提到的在12中预览，然后
for completeness I'll mention a couple
为了完整起见，我会提到几个
more which are more for future so
更多，未来更多
there's something called pattern
有一种叫做模式
matching this is an example of that to
匹配这是一个例子
get also the vision here is that we can
在这里得到的愿景是我们可以
do the same thing in switch switches
在开关中做同样的事情
going forward as well
以及前进
how many of you have done this you're
你们当中有多少人做到了
checking some instance you got and
检查您得到的一些实例并
you're checking in against the type and
您正在根据类型检查
the very next thing you need to do is to
接下来需要做的是
cast it right super annoying just
正确地投放它，超级烦人
repeating the obvious thing right so
重复明显的事情吧
basically what the first thing you can
基本上你可以做的第一件事
do obviously is just not repeat the type
显然只是不重复类型
twice using the local variable type
两次使用局部变量类型
inference but the next thing here on the
推断，但接下来的内容
pattern matching side is something along
模式匹配的一面是
these lines so you have your instance
这些行，所以你有你的实例
and instead of doing that like instance
而不是像实例那样
all plus a cast you just do sort of the
所有加上演员，你只是做
compiler does that trick for you so you
编译器会帮您解决这个问题，所以您
get the variable defined and you can use
获取定义的变量，您可以使用
it in your if statement that's for
在您的if语句中
future not well we're looking at it but
未来不好，我们正在研究它，但是
definitely not going to make thirteen
绝对不会赚十三
I'm going to say the final thing I'll
我要说的最后一件事
mention is records
提及是记录
so another common example I'm gonna say
所以我要说另一个常见的例子
so the simple sort of object data
所以简单的对象数据排序
carrier you have a couple of fields and
运营商，您有几个领域，
in order to make this complete you need
为了完成此任务，您需要
to have the constructor to gathers the
让构造函数收集
hash code equals compare if you want to
如果您想哈希码等于比较
store in a in a collection of some kind
存储在某种类型的集合中
and obviously this is all just total
显然，这只是全部
manual work to add that an error prone
手动添加容易出错的工作
and all of that right so what we're
以及所有的权利，所以我们
looking at here is providing something
看着这里提供了一些东西
that again spelling it may not be
再次拼写可能不是
spelled record in the end but something
最终的拼写记录，但有些东西
that looks like this and if you if you
看起来像这样，如果你
want the defaults then it doesn't take
想要默认值，那么不需要
more than this but if you do want to
不仅如此，但如果您确实想
override things if for example your
覆盖一些东西，例如
equals has some kind of magic property
等于具有某种魔法属性
then there you can add that yes what's
然后您可以在其中添加是的
that in line your record so I think the
符合您的记录，所以我认为
answer is just yes but it hasn't been
答案是肯定的，但事实并非如此
designed yet so so that's amber oh and I
设计好了，所以是琥珀色哦，我
should also mention by the way that the
还应提及
the JEP thing here is short for JDK
JEP是JDK的缩写
enhancement proposal and it's our way of
增强建议，这是我们的方式
documenting feature features on a high
文档功能特点高
level I'm gonna say provide some
我要说的水平提供一些
alternatives and you know details but
替代品，你知道细节，但
just a document you can go in and look
只是一个文件，你可以去看看
at these they're all on the open JDK
这些都是开放的JDK
site as well Loum is a product we're
网站以及Loum是我们的产品
looking where we're looking at improving
看我们在哪里改善
on or simplifying concurrency so today
或简化并发性，所以今天
basically I'm somewhat simplified you
基本上我有点简化你
have two different ways of handling
有两种不同的处理方式
concurrency the first one is using
并发第一个正在使用
synchronous code so you have a thread it
同步代码，所以你有一个线程
takes a request it does its thing it may
接受请求，尽其所能
call out to a database or do whatever if
调出数据库或执行任何操作
it gets blocked it's still waiting there
它被阻止了，它仍然在那里等待
patiently for the database to return the
耐心等待数据库返回
result and then at some point it returns
结果，然后在某个时候返回
the result of the transaction as a whole
整个交易的结果
super simple it's actually sort of
超级简单，实际上是
scalable right where we worked a lot in
我们经常在其中工作的可扩展性
Java to make sure that even that simple
Java确保即使如此简单
use case is working really well but
用例工作得很好，但是
there are challenges with it so if you
有挑战，所以如果你
want to scale up to the extreme and
想要扩展到极限并
those threads even though they're
这些线程，即使它们是
relative
相对的
lightweight they do tend to add up right
重量轻，他们确实倾向于加起来
so if you have a thousand requests going
因此，如果您有上千个请求
on at the same time a thousand threads
同时运行一千个线程
and that's if nothing else going to take
那就是如果没有其他需要
a lot of memory from the thread stack
线程堆栈中的大量内存
itself the alternative that you can use
本身就是您可以使用的替代方法
is a synchronous i/o and a synchronous
是同步I / O和同步
construct so in the JDK for example we
例如在JDK中构造
offer separate methods that do implement
提供确实实现的单独方法
a synchronous versions of i/o and
I / O和
they're there they're extremely scalable
他们在那里，它们具有极高的可扩展性
but they are sort of complex to use so
但是它们使用起来有点复杂
you need to to get it right let's say
您需要正确处理，假设
you now have a thread that is like
你现在有一个像
multiplexing over different connections
通过不同的连接进行多路复用
or whatever it is right and it's also so
或什么都对，它也是如此
hard to debug in profile this in the end
最后很难在配置文件中调试
so what we're trying to do with Loom
所以我们要用织机做什么
here is to make this the asynchronous
这是使它异步
case work for you as a developer as if
为您作为开发人员的案例工作
it was a synchronous if you if it was
如果是的话，那是同步的
synchronous code from the start
从一开始就同步代码
basically the the tag line is on
基本上标签线是开的
somewhere between making blocks blocking
在阻止块之间的某个地方
calls virtually free or for that sake if
几乎免费通话，或为此而致电
codes like sync but works like a sink
像同步这样的代码，但像接收器一样工作
right in in performance core concurrency
正确执行性能核心并发
made simple so the way we're
很简单，所以我们的方式
implementing this looking at
实施这一目标
implementing it is by providing
通过提供实现
something we call fibers you can think
我们可以称之为纤维的东西
of them as extremely lightweight threads
其中的线程非常轻巧
you are like you create millions of
你就像你创造了数百万
these in the same JVM or even billions
这些都在同一个JVM中，甚至数十亿
of them they're they're very very very
他们是他们非常非常非常
lightweight and the other component here
轻便的，这里的其他组件
is it's as delimited continuations here
这是定界的延续吗
mouthful but think of like execution you
满嘴，但想像处死你
call a method let's say you have a small
调用一个方法，假设您有一个小
method and it's in stuck in a while loop
方法，它陷入了while循环中
it's doing something it's computing
它正在做它正在计算的事情
something what we do with the
我们做什么的
continuations here is that we allow that
这里的延续是，我们允许
method to yield so in the middle of its
在其中间产生的方法
execution somewhere we can freeze for
我们可以冻结的地方执行
that
那
oh sorry freeze that and store it off
哦，抱歉，将其冻结并保存
somewhere on the side so like where
在侧面的某个地方
where it's running on a thread but we
它在线程上运行的位置，但是我们
can freeze that execution copy only
只能冻结该执行副本
those frames that matter to decide and
要决定的那些框架，
then have that thread continue executing
然后让那个线程继续执行
something else and what that means for
其他的东西，这意味着什么
you is that you can implement these
你是你可以实现这些
methods as if they're blocking right but
好像他们阻塞正确的方法，但是
instead of blocking they actually yield
而不是阻止他们实际上让步
in the background and we again we take
在后台，我们再次采取
that
那
small the small amount of state that is
很小的状态
running on this big dinosaur thread and
在这个大恐龙线程上运行
we copy that off and let the thread do
我们将其复制并让线程执行
something else so we open up for
还有其他事情，所以我们为
basically coding as if everything is
基本上就像一切都是编码
synchronous now the other nice part
现在同步另一个好的部分
about this is that instead of having to
关于这一点，而不是必须
supply two different versions so again I
提供两个不同的版本，所以我再次
said on the jdk side we have synchronous
说在JDK方面我们有同步
i/o and we also have a synchronous i/o
I / O，我们还有一个同步I / O
so we need to deliver both of those and
所以我们需要同时交付
if you are implementing a library
如果您正在实现一个库
framework chances are that you will in
框架的机会是你将
turn have to provide both the
轮到同时提供
synchronous version of your calls and
通话的同步版本
the synchronous version and that
同步版本和那个
obviously is a hassle right so what this
显然是一件麻烦事，所以这是什么
allows you to do is basically just
允许您做的基本上只是
improvise one version which looks like
即兴创作一个看起来像
it's synchronous and in the background
它是同步的，在后台
the JVM and the rest of the runtime
JVM和其余的运行时
takes care of it for you there is a
照顾你，有一个
prototype of this do play around with it
这个的原型玩弄它
we are investigating alternative ways of
我们正在研究替代方法
implementing this functionality as well
同时实现此功能
so that's sort of what the status of
所以这是什么状态
that product is right now Panama is a
该产品现在是巴拿马
product where we're looking into sort of
我们正在研究的产品
things that aren't native to Java so
Java本身不是的东西
Panama is a pond on either like
巴拿马是一个像
connecting the oceans one ocean being
连接海洋一个海洋被
Java and the other one being C C++
Java和另一个是C ++
native or the the continents I guess
我猜是本土或大洲
inside here is that there are a bunch of
里面是一堆
libraries that are not implemented in
未实现的库
Java or that for some reason where we
Java或出于某些原因，
want to reach out and actually access
想伸出手并实际访问
native data and that that is not on the
本机数据，但不在
Java heap in a more efficient way so
Java堆以更有效的方式
panama is exploring exactly that it's a
巴拿马正在探索这是一个
safe fast and simple way to access to
安全快捷的访问方式
call out to native functions against
呼吁反对
think C C++ and also access data that
考虑C ++，并访问数据
isn't on the Java heap and this without
不在Java堆上，而没有
having to write a single line of native
只需写一行本机
code because you can do this today there
代码，因为您今天可以在此处进行操作
is the J&amp;I interface how many people
J＆I界面有多少人
here have written J&amp;I or being done Jana
这里写过J＆I或正在做Jana
we're so sorry for you
我们为你感到抱歉
Jana is extremely hard to get right so
贾娜（Jana）很难做到正确，所以
basically for those of you who have not
基本上是为那些还没有
done this exercise if you have a
如果您有一个
favorite library that you want to call
您要调用的收藏夹库
basically this is the workflow the first
基本上这是第一个工作流程
thing you need to do is to study that
你需要做的是研究
library and understand exactly how it
图书馆，并确切地了解它
works because the next thing you need to
之所以有效，是因为接下来您需要
do is to model that whole library on the
要做的是在
Java level once you've done that you are
完成Java级别的工作后
implement you need to implement some
实现你需要实现一些
like not just the
不仅是
the Royal stubs of the methods but like
方法的皇家存根，但喜欢
actually the code to call out to native
实际调用本地代码
and you you add a bunch of methods that
然后您添加了一堆方法
are decorated with the native keyword
用本地关键字修饰
and then in the next step you use a tool
然后在下一步中使用工具
Java C in this case or Java age used to
在这种情况下，Java C或Java时代
be the name of it to generate header
作为生成标题的名称
files C C++ header files and then you
文件C C ++头文件，然后您
need to actually implement the Jana code
需要实际实现Jana代码
that bridges between the Jay and I
在我和周杰伦之间架起桥梁
headed sand Java to your favorite
带领JAVA沙到您的最爱
library and then you need to build that
库，然后您需要构建
shared library finding the tool chains
共享库查找工具链
and that's gonna be different depending
这将有所不同，具体取决于
on which platform you are on and then
您在哪个平台上，然后
finally you can actually start using the
最后，您实际上可以开始使用
code right and God forbid somebody goes
代码正确，上帝禁止某人去
in and actually changes that library
并实际上更改该库
you're trying to mom model because now
你想妈妈做模特，因为现在
you need to go in and change everything
你需要去改变一切
right that's been unfortunate so what
对，那一直很不幸，那又怎样
we're trying to do is to basically cut
我们试图做的是基本上削减
cut away like the first things here all
像第一件事一样切掉
the ones that are error-prone because
那些容易出错的原因是
every single step here you can get wrong
每一步都可能出错
in J and I especially the branching
在J和我特别是分支
layer is extremely easy to get wrong you
层非常容易出错
forget to free up a resource or
忘记释放资源或
something like that so basically this is
像这样的东西，基本上这是
the new model we're envisioning you're
我们设想您的新模式
using a tool to generate things and the
使用工具生成事物
things here are actually Java classes or
这里的东西实际上是Java类或
interfaces more specifically so
界面更具体如此
basically this is all automated you
基本上这都是自动化的
pointed out that a library or a header
指出一个库或标题
file and it generates Java code for you
文件，它会为您生成Java代码
and then you can just start calling
然后你就可以开始打电话了
those Java methods you have not like
你不喜欢的那些Java方法
written a single line of native code and
编写了一行本地代码，然后
you you can now use that library
您现在可以使用该库
obviously you still have to understand
显然，您仍然必须了解
the library about to use but at least
该库即将使用，但至少
there's less in the way let's say you'll
可以说您会减少
do that right metropolis is a also a one
做到正确的大都会也是一个
of those big projects it is exploring
正在探索的那些大型项目中
how we can use Java more to implement
我们如何更多地使用Java来实现
the Java Runtime itself so a large part
Java Runtime本身很大一部分
of Java and especially the core
Java特别是核心
libraries are obviously implemented in
库显然是在
Java but the JVM is still native code
Java，但JVM仍是本机代码
and the first thing we're looking into
而我们正在研究的第一件事
here is how we can move the job the JIT
这就是我们如何将JIT移交给工作
compiler that lives inside of the JVM so
驻留在JVM内部的编译器
the compiler that takes bytecode Java
需要字节码Java的编译器
bytecode and turns it into efficient
字节码并将其转换为有效的
machine code if you so will so that's
机器代码，如果您愿意，那是
the first thing we're looking into so
我们正在研究的第一件事
today we have two different JIT
今天我们有两个不同的准时制
compilers in the JVM there's C one also
JVM中的编译器也有C语言
known as the client compiler and seat
被称为客户端编译器和座位
which is the server the fully optimizing
完全优化的服务器
compiler that we have so c2 is sort of
我们拥有的编译器因此c2有点
reaching its complexity but yet we we
达到其复杂性，但我们
put a lot of good stuff into c2 but it's
在c2中放了很多好东西，但是
sort of time to to look at it like what
有点时间去看它像什么
what does the future look like the next
未来会是什么样
10 15 years or 20 and it also turns out
10 15年或20年，事实证明
that a lot of these products have a big
这些产品很多都很大
significant impact on the compiler we do
对我们所做的编译器有重大影响
need a lot of work in the compiler the
需要在编译器中做很多工作
compiler is sort of the the secret
编译器是个秘密
weapon that we have in the DM and that
我们在DM中拥有的武器
needs to work really really well for all
需要让所有人真正工作得很好
kinds of cone shapes so for a lot of the
各种各样的圆锥形
products we do need work in the JIT so
我们确实需要在JIT中工作的产品
making it easier to improve on our death
使我们更容易改善死亡
going forward is important so what do
前进很重要，所以该怎么办
you do when you have two of something
当你有两个东西时你会做
and you want to get down to one you add
而您想下降到一个添加
a third in this case we're adding
在这种情况下，我们要添加三分之一
something called growl growl is a JIT
所谓的咆哮咆哮是准时制
compiler implemented in Java and we like
用Java实现的编译器，我们喜欢
to think that Java again is is a good
再次认为Java是一个好习惯
language to to implement things in in
实现事物的语言
general so why not the compiler pros
一般，为什么不编译专家
include things like it's again faster to
包括类似的东西
do development going forward it's also
做发展，这也是
easy it's a lower barrier to entry if
很容易，如果
you want to experiment with things you
你想尝试一些你喜欢的东西
don't have to build rebuild the JVM you
不必构建重新构建JVM
can actually work on the Java level and
实际上可以在Java级别上工作，并且
get all the Idid support and code
获得所有Idid支持和代码
browsing and all of that there are a few
浏览，所有这些都有
products that are small in nature novel
自然界中新颖的产品
they touch on them really quickly one is
他们很快就接触到它们
called SCARA this product is looking at
这个产品叫SCARA
modernizing the developer experience for
现代化的开发人员体验
us that work on the jdk itself so that
我们在jdk本身上工作，以便
that code development is currently
该代码开发目前
happening on I'm gonna call it aging and
发生在我要称之为老化和
not necessarily aged with Dignity code
不一定年龄与尊严代码
the infrastructure so this is
基础设施，所以这是
specifically around code reviews and SEM
特别是围绕代码审查和SEM
like yeah taking care of the code itself
就像是照顾代码本身
so what we're investing here if we
所以我们要在这里投资什么
should move over from we're currently
应该从我们目前的位置移开
using mercurial if we should move over
如果我们应该走过去的话
maybe to get it does seem like there are
也许得到它确实好像有
many more tools that support get the
更多支持的工具
underarmor q4 material and also
装甲q4材料以及
leveraging existing hosting providers
利用现有的托管服务提供商
like yet lab or github things like that
像是实验室或github之类的东西
lots of exciting stuff happening here
这里发生了很多令人兴奋的事情
Portola George mentioned on his slide
乔治·波托拉在幻灯片中提到
earlier as well is where we're looking
也是我们正在寻找的地方
at
在
making sure that the other works really
确保其他作品真的
really well in containers how many
容器中真的很好
people in hair here have heard about
这里的头发人都听说过
Alpine Linux ooh
高山Linux哦
surprisingly many how many people in
令人惊讶的是，有多少人
here would like to see a port of the JDK
这里想看看JDK的端口
- Alpine Linux ok few answers how many
-Alpine Linux好的几个答案几个
people would like to help maintain is
人们想帮助维持的是
imported do let us know we're trying to
进口确实让我们知道我们正在努力
gauge the interest and figure out if
衡量兴趣并弄清楚是否
it's worth moving forward with this
值得继续前进
there is a product where like the JDK
有像JDK这样的产品
actually it builds and runs stuff but we
实际上，它可以构建并运行东西，但是我们
haven't done all the testing we know
尚未完成我们知道的所有测试
when we do to certify that it likely is
当我们确实证明它可能是
functionally correct CGC is a product
功能正确的CGC是产品
where we're looking at a garbage
我们在看垃圾
collector that is that has yet like soft
像软的收藏家
but still pretty good let's say
但还是可以说
guarantee surround pause times so the
确保环绕声暂停时间，因此
goal of this project is to support very
该项目的目标是非常支持
very large heaps so I think we just
非常大的堆，所以我认为我们只是
upped I can't remember right now we
我现在不记得了
upped it to 16 terabytes or or maybe
将其提高到16 TB，或者也许
more but in our case large heaps with
更多，但在我们的情况下
like while still keeping the post times
就像在保持发布时间一样
really really low so the goal is 10
真的很低，所以目标是10
milliseconds and we're actually below
毫秒，我们实际上低于
that right now but at the same time one
现在，但与此同时
of the other things that we take pride
我们引以为傲的其他事情
in here isn't you not having to tune
在这里，您不必调整
things it should just work out of the
它应该可以解决的问题
box without that requirement and and
没有该要求的盒子，以及
we're trying to do this while keeping
我们正在努力做到这一点，同时保持
the throughput overhead low so the goal
吞吐量开销低，因此目标
is 15% seemed like a nice round number
是15％似乎是一个不错的整数
where most people can accept the
大多数人可以接受的地方
trade-off and we're doing it really well
权衡，我们做得很好
there as well and then finally I'll just
在那里，然后最后我只是
mention I probably called jf or or JDK
提到我大概叫jf或JDK
flight recorder so imagine that you're
飞行记录仪，让您想象自己
working in a project and you were
在一个项目中工作，你曾经
actually on call in some way so
实际上以某种方式待命
typically you know you can bet that it's
通常你知道你可以打赌它是
like Sunday or Saturday evening or
例如周日或周六晚上或
something like something happens SLA is
发生类似SLA的事情是
breached somewhere and the problem is
突破某处，问题是
you have no idea what's going on right
你不知道发生了什么事
so the first thing you do either work
所以你要做的第一件事
first thing but like at some point you
第一件事，但就像在某个时候
add some logging and you try to get more
添加一些日志记录，您尝试获得更多
information
信息
logging unfortunately comes with
不幸的是，日志附带
performance overhead so after a while
性能开销，所以过了一会儿
nothing's been found you need to remove
没有发现您需要删除的内容
the logging because you don't want to
记录，因为你不想
pay for the additional servers and
支付额外的服务器和
remove the logging in obviously next
删除日志显然下一步
Saturday at 7 p.m. again same thing
星期六晚上7点再次发生同样的事情
happens right j4 is trying to solve
发生正确的j4试图解决
exactly that problem by piggybacking on
piggy带上正是这个问题
a lot of what the JVM already does
JVM已经做的很多事情
so it's collecting a lot of fine-grained
所以它收集了很多细粒度的
information about the system itself both
有关系统本身的信息
inside the VM but there's also an API
在VM内，但也有一个API
you can use to put user defined events
您可以用来放置用户定义的事件
into that same stream and it's doing
进入同一流，它正在
this in like the how should I put this
就像我应该怎么把这个
we're trying to make sure it's designed
我们正在尝试确保它的设计
to be all in production that's that's
完全是在生产中
the first thing to keep in mind you can
首先要记住的是
use this during development obviously
在开发过程中显然使用它
but it's designed to be on in production
但它被设计用于生产中
and it's helping you collect almost like
它可以帮助您收集几乎
too much information it's it's the
太多的信息是
default settings will collect you know
默认设置将收集您知道的信息
enough information for most cases but
在大多数情况下，信息足够，但是
but it's I don't know how to put this in
但是我不知道怎么把它放进去
are there any other way that it's
还有其他方法吗
extremely powerful so you know have a
非常强大，所以您知道
look and tell us what you want what to
看看并告诉我们您想要什么
see going forward so last slide I
看到前进，所以我最后一张幻灯片
promised to give you some links to early
答应给您一些早期链接
access binaries so again we are counting
访问二进制文件，所以我们再次数
on your feedback and we need your help
根据您的反馈意见，我们需要您的帮助
to make sure that what we develop the
确保我们开发的
future products that you actually make
您实际制造的未来产品
sense that you know you feel natural to
感觉自己知道自己对
work with and all that and also to to
与之合作，并致力于
make sure help ensure that the projects
确保帮助确保项目
the greece's we do actually the you know
希腊的我们实际上是在做
work right that there are no issues so
工作正常，没有问题，所以
for jdk 13 which is GA september
适用于GA 9月的jdk 13
something something it's actually a
有些东西实际上是
pretty good place to be right now
现在相当不错的地方
because like these six-month releases is
因为像这六个月的发行版一样
like where we found that what we need to
就像我们发现需要的地方
do is to make sure that the quality
要做的是确保质量
remains high on every single push we do
我们所做的每一次推动都保持高水平
and what that basically does is that
基本上就是
when a release comes along it's like a
当发布时，就像
non-event it's like we draw a line and
非事件就像我们画一条线，
say here what the here's what went into
在这里说这是什么
this release and then next three months
此版本，然后接下来的三个月
we just more or less sit around their
我们或多或少地坐在他们周围
old thumps and it's like and then so DGA
旧的重击，然后像DGA
comes along right then it's like yeah
马上就来了，就像是
fair enough we almost forgot about the
足够公平，我们几乎忘记了
JDK twelve released just a few weeks ago
JDK十二周前发布
so in September we're releasing 13 we
所以在9月我们将发布13个
are publishing on a weekly basis early
每周提前出版一次
access binaries for 13 so please pick up
访问二进制文件为13，所以请拿起
try them out and let us know
试试看，让我们知道
if if you find any issues or for that
如果您发现任何问题或为此
sake even if you like what's in there
即使你喜欢里面的东西
right and it positive feedback is also
对，它的正面反馈也
nice to get some from time to time and
很高兴不时得到一些
then for the projects these are a few of
那么对于项目来说，
the projects that we're also publishing
我们也在发布的项目
early access binaries for so again if
早期访问二进制文件，如果再次
you're curious to try out Valhalla or
您很好奇尝试Valhalla或
Panama or we have a J package product as
巴拿马，或者我们有J包装产品
well now that's where you can find them
好吧，现在您可以在其中找到它们
ok thank you Michael so hopefully this
好的，谢谢迈克尔，希望如此
was useful getting you know both a
让您同时了解两个
little bit of an overview of sort of the
有点概述
status and where things are with Java
状态以及Java的状况
how we go about developing it and and
我们如何发展它，以及
and finally a deep dive into a bunch of
最后深入一堆
the projects that we're working on
我们正在从事的项目
trying to keep making it better for you
试图让它变得更好
so I think we have time for maybe a
所以我认为我们有时间可能
couple of questions
几个问题
[Applause]
[掌声]